Guide to the Rice University Early Land Deeds, Contracts and Related Records, 1830-1969 UA 222
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series I: Rice Land Deeds, 1830-1966; 144825; 39 Linear Feet
  - Texas Counties, 144826
    - Harris County, 145136
      - Acquisition, 66 acres in Pleasant W. Rose Survey from August Warnecke, Harris Co., 1909, 145162 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Acquisition, 24 acres in Pleasant W. Rose Survey from August Warnecke, Harris Co., 1909, 145161 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Sale, 125 acres in Gamble Survey to George H. Hermann, Harris Co., 1908, 145160 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Lease agreement, 10 acres in Gamble Survey with Charles F. Weber, Harris Co., 1910, 1912, 145159 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence concerning sale/purchase of various tracts in the P.W. Rose Survey, Harris Co., 1909, 145158 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Field notes from various tracts in Pleasant W. Rose & Gamble Survey's, Harris Co., 1914, 1920, 145157 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Purchase, 9.734 acres in Pleasant W. Rose Survey from W.T. Carter, Harris Co., 1869, 1896-1910, 145156 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Surveys, Harris Co., 1892, 1908-1909, 1917-1920, 145153
        - Beldin Survey, Harris Co., 1908-1909, 145155 (Box 18, Folder 10, Subfolder 1)
        - A.C. Reynolds Survey, Harris Co., 1892, 1917-1920, 145154 (Box 18, Folder 10, Subfolder 2)
      - Donnelly Survey - K.E. Choate and Mills Bennett Production, Co., Harris Co., 1932-1933, 145151
        - A. Mills Bennett Production Co., 1932-1933, 145152 (Box 18, Folder 11, Subfolder 1)
      - Encroachments on Donnelly Survey, Harris Co., 1934-1936, 145150 (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Donnelly Survey - Metzler tennancy, surveys, reports, maps, lumber estimates, Harris Co., 1872-1873, 1906-1942, 145149 (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - William C. Sypert Survey, Harris Co., 1887-1894, 1917-1918, 1929-1930, 1944, 1956, 145147
        - Easement correspondence for Shell Pipeline Corp., 1929, 145148 (Box 18, Folder 14, Subfolder 1)
      - Conveyance, Harris Co., 1881, 145146 (Box 18, Folder 15)
      - Quit Claim Deeds, 145141
        - Tobias Sakowitz, et al, Harris Co., 1927, 145145 (Box 18, Folder 16, Subfolder 1)
        - Main St. Holding Co., for Main St. auditorium, Harris Co., 1926, 145144 (Box 18, Folder 16, Subfolder 2)
        - R.T. Andrews, Harris Co., 1929, 145143 (Box 18, Folder 16, Subfolder 3)
        - S.J. Swenson, "Allen's Addition" in Harris Co., 1909-1911, 145142 (Box 18, Folder 16, Subfolder 4)
      - Sale, 9,449 acres Westmoreland Farms, Rice Ranch to South End Land Co., Harris Co., 1892, 1904-1923, 145138
        - Memo, releases of land to South End Land Co., 1908-1923, 145140 (Box 19)
        - Abstract of title to Westmoreland Farms, 1910, 145139 (Box 19)
      - Sale, 9,449 acres Westmoreland Farms, Rice Ranch to South End Land Co., Harris Co., 1910-1927, 1939, 145137 (Box 20, Folder 1-3)
    - Hill County, 145131
      - Joseph Punchard Survey, Hill Co., 1902-1908, 145135 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Sale, 620 acres in Punchard Survey to L.T. Cox, Hill Co., 1919-1921, 145134 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - Sale, 619 acres in Punchard Survey to O.M. Weatherby, Hill Co., 1919-1923, 145133 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Sale, 619 acres in Punchard Survey to O.M. Weatherby, Hill Co., 1922-1927, 145132 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Hopkins County, 145129
      - Cultivation of Rice Institute Property, various lots, Richland, Hopkins Co., 1935, 145130 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Houston County, 145127
      - Sale, 4 lots in City of Kennard to C.A. Westerman, Houston Co., 1944, 145128 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Hunt County, 145124
      - Caleb P. Alexander Survey, Hunt Co., 1886-1912, 145126 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - Sale, 320 acres in C.P. Alexander Survey to P.A. Peak, Hunt Co., 1913, 145125 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Irion County, 145119
      - Sale, 640 acres in Joseph Blessman Survey to Jesse Burke, Irion Co., 1937, 145123 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, titles, agreements, etc. concerning Joseph Blessman Survey, Irion Co., 1859-1943, 145121
        - Grant to heirs of Joseph Blessman land in Bexar Co., 1859, 145122 (Box 21, Folder 10, Subfolder 1)
      - Correspondence, contracts, notes, etc. concerning lands in Irion Co., 1887, 1920-1933, 145120 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Jasper County, 145095
      - John James Survey, Jasper Co., 1869-1917, 145118 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Lost land, John James Survey, Jasper Co., 1907, 145117 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Lurana Allen Survey, Jasper Co., 1870-1911, 145116 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Joseph Lane Survey, Jasper Co., 1881-1885, 1909, 145115 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - W.H. Smith Survey, Jasper Co., 1882-1917, 145114 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Andrew F. Smyth Survey, Jasper Co., 1858, 1883-1911, 145113 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - George W. Smyth Survey, Jasper Co., 1852-1883, 1908-1938, 145112 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Re-resurvey of Smith/Smyth Surveys, Jasper Co., 1917-1920, 145111 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Robert M. Williamson Survey, Jasper Co., 1843, 1869, 1891, 1907-1918, 145110 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Polly Youngblood Survey, suit Whitehead vs. Washburn, Jasper Co., 1924-1927, 145109 (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - Polly Youngblood Survey, Jasper and Newton Counties, 1876-1881, 1900-1918, 145108 (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - Tax deed surveys, Jasper Co., 1884, 145107 (Box 22, Folder 12)
      - P.B. Pry Survey, Jasper Co., 1850, 1858, 1883, 1907-1912, 145106 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - P.B. Pry resurvey, Jasper Co., 1911-1917, 145105 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Sale, 10 acres in George Smyth Survey to Jasper County Lumber Company, Jasper Co., 1920-1935, 145104 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Sale, 1740 acres in Youngblood Survey to L.H. Marshburn, jasper and Newton Counties, 1919-1920, 145103 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Sale, 354 acres of Lane Survey to O.M. Stone, Jasper Co., 1910-1911, 145102 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Sale, 580 acres in R.M. Williamson Survey to Amos Richardson, Jasper Co., 1911, 145101 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Sale, 581 acres in John James Survey to Kirby Lumber Co., 1909, 1912, 1921, 145100 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Sale, timber in John James Survey to Kirby Lumber Co., Jasper Co., 1916, 145099 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Sale, 177 acres in Lurana Allen Survey to Alex Gilmer, Jasper Co., 1908-1918, 145098 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Early Jasper County surveys, 1859, 1870-1871, 1881-1882, 145097 (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Contract with Jasper Richardson to look after land in Jasper Co., 1909, 145096 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Jones County, 145090
      - Jones County Lands, 1871-1906, 145093 (Box 24, Folder 1)
        - Prairie Dog problem, 1904-1905, 145094 (Box 24, Folder 1, Subfolder 1)
      - Harrison County School lands survey, Jones Co., 1880-1892, 145092 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Harris County school leagues, #333-334, Jones County, 1879, 1898-1917, 145091 (Box 24, Folder 3-4)
    - Kaufman County, 145085
      - Thomas Beedy Survey, Kaufman Co., 1908-1914, 145089 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Sale, 905 acres in Thomas Beedy Survey to J.A. Coleman, Kaufman Co., 1914-1921, 145087 (Box 24, Folder 6)
        - Contracts with J.A. Coleman, Kaufman Co., 1907-1915, 145088 (Box 24, Folder 6, Subfolder 1)
      - Deed copy, Kaufman Co., 1905, 145086 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Kleberg County, 145083
      - Mineral Lease, Mrs. H.M. King to Humble Oil Co., Kleberg Co., (King Ranch area), 1922, 145084 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Lampasas County, 145074
      - Sale, 45 acres in L.H.W. Johnson Survey to E.M. Howard, Lampasas Co., 1908-1910, 145082 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Sale, 2 lots in Lampasas Springs First Addition to T.D. Larue, Lampasas Co., 1916, 145081 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Sale, 26 acres in L.H.W. Johnson League to B.H. Walser, Lampasas Co., 1916, 1919, 145080 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Sale, 540 acres in H.T. & B. Railroad Company Survey to C.R. Craft, Lampasas Co., 1916, 1919, 145079 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Sale, 1280 acres in G.B. & N. and H.T. & B Railroad Company Survey to J.B. Taylor, Lampasas Co., 1914-1919, 145078 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Sale, 1 block in City of Lampasas to A.P. Anderson, Lampasas Co., 1917, 145077 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Sale, 1 lot in L.H.W. Johnson Survey to George D. Zuilgy. Lampasas Co., 1917, 145076 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Lampasas County lands, 1870-1898, 1908, 1917-1918, 145075 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Leon County, 145070
      - Leon County Lands, 1876-1877, 1908-1917, 145073 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - Leon County Abstracts: Ramon de la Garza XI Survey, 1910; Aaron West Survey, 1908, 145072 (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - Lease, 350 acres in A. West Survey to L.D. Sims & D.F. Fortson, Leon Co., 1917-1918. 1953, 145071 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Lee County, 145051
      - Lee County lands, 1907-1922, 145069 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Abstract, David Frost Survey, Lee Co., 1907, 145068 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Abstract, George W. Lowder Survey, Lee Co., 1907, 145067 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Abstract, Silas Woods Survey, Lee Co., 1907, 1910, 145066 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Abstract, Calvin Chaney Survey, Lee Co., 1907, 145065 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Sale, 35.5 acres in Silas Woods Survey to Ed E. Fischer, Lee Co., 1918, 145064 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Sale, 64.5 acres, Barker and Lowder Surveys to John C. Parker, Lee Co., 1918-1919, 145063 (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - Sale, 691 acres, Woods and Chaney Surveys to Lee Wilson, Lee Co., 1918-1919, 145062 (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Sale, 117 acres of Silas Woods Survey to Theo Tonn, Lee Co., 1910, 145061 (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - Sale, 8 acres in Jesse Barker Survey to P.L. Guffin, Lee Co., 1912-1913, 145060 (Box 26, Folder 10)
      - Sale, 67 acres of J. Richardson Survey to Dennis Colvin, Lee Co., 1910, 145059 (Box 26, Folder 11)
      - Sale, 23 acres in D. Frost Survey to Town of Giddings, Lee Co., 1914, 145058 (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - Sale, 314 acres in Frost & Lowder Surveys to E.A. Domaschk, Lee Co., 1917, 145057 (Box 26, Folder 13)
      - Sale, 496 acres in Silas Woods and William Thompson Surveys to Lee Wilson, J.W. Tate & John Knox, Lee Co., 1917-1918, 145056 (Box 26, Folder 14)
      - Lease, 871 acres in Calvin Cheney Survey to Fronia Longley, Lee Co., 1918, 145055 (Box 26, Folder 15)
      - Lease, 194 acres in G.W. Lowder Survey to E.A. Domaschk, Lee Co., 1917-1918, 145054 (Box 26, Folder 16)
      - Deeds, title papers, town lots, Giddings, Lee Co., 1927, 145053 (Box 26, Folder 17)
      - Various deeds and title papers, Lee Co., 1887-1923, 145052 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Limestone County, 145027
      - Sale, 47 acres in McIntyre (McIntire) Survey to W.P. Alexander, Limestone Co., 1910-1915, 145050 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Sale, 1300 acres of McIntyre (McIntire) and Bass Surveys to J.A. McKenzie, et al, Limestone Co., 1910-1911, 145049 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Sale, for right-of-way, Division W, City of Mexia to State of Texas, Limestone Co., 1935-1936, 145048 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Sale, easement in city of Mexia to city of Mexia, Limestone Co., 1954, 145047 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Lease, 22 lots in city of Mexia to city of Mexia, Limestone Co., 1936, 1942, 145046 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Lease, 18 lots in city of Mexia to Leonard Tidwell, Limestone Co., 1942, 145045 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - A. Bass Survey, Limestone Co., 1887, 1908-1910, 145044 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - Robert McIntire (McIntyre) Survey, Limestone Co., 1889, 1909, 145043 (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - Deeds, titles, papers, town lots, Limestone Co., 145039
        - Kosse, 1922-1934, 145042 (Box 27, Folder 9, Subfolder 1)
        - Mexia, 1918, 145041 (Box 27, Folder 9, Subfolder 2)
        - Thornton, 1934-1935, 145040 (Box 27, Folder 9, Subfolder 3)
      - Cancelled deeds, Limestone Co., 1921-1923, 145038 (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - Paving in Mexia, Limestone Co., 1922-1956, 145037 (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - Reconveyances, deeds, title papers, Limestone Co., 1922-1939, 145033
        - Recovery of property, claimed adversely, Kosse, Limestone Co., 1922, 145036 (Box 27, Folder 12, Folder 1)
        - Reconveyance, lots 1-5, 9-10, block 113; Lots 3-10, block 114, Thornton, Limestone Co., 1939, 145035 (Box 27, Folder 12, Subfolder 2)
        - Reconveyance, lots 1-4, 17-18, block 10, Limestone Co., 1929-1933, 145034 (Box 27, Folder 12, Subfolder 3)
      - Various deeds, title papers, Limestone Co., 1905-1924, 145032 (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - Various deeds, title papers, Limestone Co., 1918-1923, 145028
        - Title and reconveyance of lot 6, block 37 from J.J. Pearson, Mexia, Limestone Co., 1920-1922, 145031 (Box 27, Folder 14, Subfolder 1)
        - Title and reconveyance of lot 8 block 119 from Mrs. Aoa Ball, Mexia, Limestone Co., 1921-1923, 145030 (Box 27, Folder 14, Subfolder 2)
        - J.E. Frost foreclosure, Mexia, Limestone Co., 1922-1923, 145029 (Box 27, Folder 14, Subfolder 3)
    - Madison County, 145024
      - George A. Lamb Survey, Madison Co., 1896-1916, 145026 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Sale, 126 acres in George A. Lamb Survey to J.R. Hightower, Madison Co., 1913-1919, 145025 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Marion County, 145021
      - Acquisition, 150 acres in David Lane Survey from L.G. & C.C. Braden, Marion Co., 1938-1939, 145023 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Sale, 150 acres in Lower Headright Survey to T.D. hill, Marion Co., 1943, 145022 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Mills County, 145019
      - Title papers, Mills Co., 1907-1917, 145020 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Montgomery County, 144976
      - Title papers to land sold, Montgomery Co., 1907, 1923, 1932, 145014
        - Stansberry (Stansbury) Survey, Montgomery Co., 1907, 145018 (Box 28, Folder 6, Subfolder 1)
        - Report on timber land in Jones, Stansberry (Stansbury) and Robinson Surveys, Montgomery Co., 1923, 145017 (Box 28, Folder 6, Subfolder 2)
        - Lorenzo Jones Survey, Montgomery Co., 1907, 145016 (Box 28, Folder 6, Subfolder 3)
        - Quit Claim Deed, Joseph Lindley League, Montgomery Co., 1932, 145015 (Box 28, Folder 6, Subfolder 4)
      - Joseph M. Robinson Survey, Montgomery Co., 1908-1924, 145013 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Robins, Jones and Stansbury Surveys, Montgomery Co., 1920-1924, 145012 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Abstract, Wilson Lang Survey, Montgomery Co., 1923, 145011 (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - Sale, 679 acres of timber on J.E. Lewis and William B. Bridges Surveys to Keystone Mills Co., Montgomery Co., 1907-1908, 145010 (Box 28, Folder 10)
      - Sale, timber, Frederick Survey to Keefer Lumber Co., Montgomery Co., 1925-1931, 145009 (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - Sale, 300 acres of M.R. Goheen tract to J.C. Hutcheson, Montgomery Co., 1907-1909, 145008 (Box 28, Folder 12)
      - Sale, 5 acres in A.P. Fredericks Survey to Montgomery Co., 1911, 145007 (Box 28, Folder 13)
      - Sale, timber in A.P. Fredericks Survey to Burkitt and Barnes, Montgomery Co., 1912-1914, 145006 (Box 28, Folder 14)
      - Sale, 12 acres in A.P. Fredericks Survey to Montgomery Co., 1928-1929, 145005 (Box 28, Folder 15)
      - Sale, timber on 1464 acres in A.P. Fredericks Survey to Foster Lumber Co., Montgomery Co., 1941, 145004 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Sale, timber on 82 acres of J.E. Lewis Survey to Crockett martin, Montgomery Co., 1928, 145003 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - Sale, timber on 1636 acres of Lewis, Bridges & Blake Surveys to Conroe Lumber Company, Montgomery Co., 1936-1938, 145002 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Sale, timber on 1640 acres in Robinson, Jones & Stansbury (Stansberry) Surveys to the Thompson Brothers, Montgomery Co., 1944, 145001 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - Sale, 2 acres in A.P. Fredericks Survey to State of Texas, Montgomery Co., 1947, 145000 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - Sale, timber, 1624 acres in Lewis, Bridges & Blake Surveys and 1464 acres in A.P. Fredericks Survey to Timber Lumber Company, Montgomery Co., 1947-1950, 144999 (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - Lease, 600 acres in Bennett Blake Survey to W.B. Nelson, Montgomery Co., 1960, 144998 (Box 29, Folder 7)
      - Lease, 1000 acres in A.P. Fredericks Survey to Marion F. Casey, Montgomery Co., 1953, 1963, 144997 (Box 29, Folder 8)
      - Lease, 961 acres in J.E. Lewis & William Bridges Surveys to Atlantic Refining Company, Montgomery Co., 1943, 144996 (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - Lease, 500 acres in J.E. Lewis Survey to P.M. Bussell and Frank Kauskopf, Montgomery Co., 1966, 144995 (Box 29, Folder 10)
      - Lease, 500 acres in J.E. Lewis Survey to G.R. Campbell, Montgomery Co., 1960, 144994 (Box 29, Folder 11)
      - Lease, 400 acres in J.E. Lewis Survey to G.R. Gupton, Montgomery Co., 1952, 1956, 144993 (Box 29, Folder 12)
      - Lease, 200 acres in J.E. Lewis Survey to C.N. Nicholson, Montgomery Co., 1961-1963, 144992 (Box 29, Folder 13)
      - Magnolia Foliage contract, A.P. Fredericks Survey, with W.F. Castrow, Montgomery Co., 1955, 144991 (Box 29, Folder 14)
      - Lease, 600 acres in William B. Bridges Survey to Curtis M. Parker, Montgomery Co., 1963-1965, 144990 (Box 29, Folder 15)
      - Montgomery Co., 1863-1891, 1906-1932, 1952:, 144985
        - J.E. Lewis (F.A. Rice) Survey, 1906-1932, 144989 (Box 29, Folder 16, Subfolder 1)
        - United Gas Pipeline Easement, 144988 (Box 29, Folder 16, Subfolder 2)
        - Deeds and correspondence concerning information on abstracts, 1879-1925, 144987 (Box 29, Folder 16, Subfolder 3)
        - Easement for right-of-way to Gulf State Utilities Company, 1928-1930, 144986 (Box 29, Folder 16, Subfolder 4)
      - Montgomery County, 1850-1883, 1907-1918, 1925-1951:, 144977
        - William B. Bridges Survey, 1850, 1866, 1907-1918, 144984 (Box 29, Folder 17, Subfolder 1)
        - Sale, 122 acres in A.P. Fredericks Survey to R.W. Wier, et al, 1907-1937, 144983 (Box 29, Folder 17, Subfolder 2)
        - A.P. Fredericks Survey, 1907-1910, 1938, 144982 (Box 29, Folder 17, Subfolder 3)
        - Southwestern Bell easement for telephone line, 1950, 144981 (Box 29, Folder 17, Subfolder 4)
        - Gulf States Utilities Company, easement for service line, 1939, 144980 (Box 29, Folder 17, Subfolder 5)
        - Trunkline Gas Company, easement for gas transmission line, 1951, 144979 (Box 29, Folder 17, Subfolder 6)
        - Bennett Blake Survey, 1907-1932, 144978 (Box 29, Folder 17, Subfolder 7)
    - Navarro County, 144961
      - John Choate and John White Surveys, Navarro Co., 1907, 144975 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - H.W. Cook Survey, Navarro Co., 1898-1916, 144974 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Abstract, John Choate and John White Surveys, Navarro Co., 1907, 144973 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - Sale, 246 acres of Cook Survey to W.S. Slaughter, Navarro Co., 1910, 1913, 144972 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Sale, 3/4 acre in John Choate Survey to First Baptist Church, Navarro Co., 1911-1913, 144971 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Sale, 190 acres in Choate Survey to J.H. Edgar, Navarro Co., 1916-1921, 144970 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Sale, 231 acres in John White and John Choate Surveys to various buyers, Navarro Co., 1917-1928, 144969 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Sale, 59 acres in John Choate Survey to B.L. Swick, Navarro Co., 1917, 144968 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - Sale, 4 acres in John Choate Survey to Houston & Texas Railroad, Navarro Co., 1913-1917, 144967 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - Cancelled Deeds, Navarro Co., 1921-1923, 144966 (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - Sheriff's Deeds, Navarro Co., 1925, 144965 (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - Deeds concerning lands held by Jensen, Loftin and Shields, Navarro and Hopkins Counties, 1923-1925, 144964 (Box 30, Folder 12)
      - Various deeds and title papers, Navarro Co., 1870, 1911-1926 - Reconveyance, E.H. Buie, lot 5 block 29, Richland, 1925-1926, 144962 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Newton County, 144927
      - Polly Youngblood Survey, Newton Co., 1857-1900, 1915, 1919, 144960 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Anthony J. Gilchrist Survey, Newton Co., 1908-1915, 144959 (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - James Gray Survey, abstract and lawsuit, Newton, 1892-1922, 144958 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Timothy D. Porter Survey, Newton Co., 1916-1917, 144957 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - John Miller Survey, Newton Co., 1892-1915, 144956 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Polly Youngblood Survey, Newton Co., 1884-1925, 144955 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Polly Youngblood Survey, Newton and Jasper Counties, 1908-1920, 144954 (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Abstract, part of James Gray Survey, Newton Co., 1907, 144953 (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Transcripts of land dispute, Rice Institute vs. Giles Singletary, Newton Co., 1908, 144952 (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Sale, 200 acres of Moyer Survey to E.E. Macdonald, Newton Co., 1925-1926, 144951 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Sale, 738 acres in James Gray Survey to Giles Singletary, Newton Co., 1909, 1921, 144950 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - Sale, timber on 320 acres of M.B. Lewis Survey to Miller-Link Lumber Co., Newton Co., (no content), 144949 (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Sale, 1118 acres in Thomas Tanner Survey to W. Heyman, Newton Co., 1911-1913, 144948 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Sale, timber on 320 acres of M.B. Lewis Survey to Thomas Williams, Newton Co., 1928-1929, 144947 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - Sale, timber in Gilchrist and Miller Surveys, correspondence only, Newton Co., 1915-1917, 144946 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - Sale, timber on 320 acres in M.B. Lewis Survey to E.E. McDonald, Newton Co., 1942, 144945 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - Sale, 315 acres in Timothy D. Porter Survey to Alexander Gilmer Lumber Company, Newton Co., 1908-1918, 144944 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Sale, 160 acres in W.F. Tanner Survey to L. Miller, Newton, Co., 1908, 1917-1918, 144943 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - Newton County, 1882-1892, 1907, 1917-1926, 144939 (Box 32, Folder 10)
        - Various Survey information, 1907, 1923, 144942 (Box 32, Folder 10, Subfolder 1)
        - William F. Tanner Survey, correspondence, deeds, abstracts, 1882-1892. 1907, 144941 (Box 32, Folder 10, Subfolder 2)
        - P.D. Moyer Survey, Newton Co., 1917-1926, 144940 (Box 32, Folder 10, Subfolder 3)
      - Peter D. Moyer Survey, Newton Co., 1882, 1887, 1908-1924, 144933
        - Claim discrepancy, 1915, 1924, 144938 (Box 32, Folder 11, Subfolder 1)
        - Correspondence concerning various small payments, 1909, 144937 (Box 32, Folder 11, Subfolder 2)
        - Information concerning Mary Irvine(?) vs. Rice lawsuit, 1908, 1917-1922, 144936 (Box 32, Folder 11, Subfolder 3)
        - Correspondence concerning Rice Institute vs. Willette lawsuit, 1917-1919, 144935 (Box 32, Folder 11, Subfolder 4)
        - Tenancy agreement with John Ervine, 1916, 144934 (Box 32, Folder 11, Subfolder 5)
      - Newton County lands, 1882-1937:, 144928
        - 320 acres in Martin B. Lewis Survey, 1907-1917, 144932 (Box 32, Folder 12, Subfolder 1)
        - Oil, gas & mineral lease to Republic Production Company in Martin Lewis Survey, 1933-1937, 144931 (Box 32, Folder 12, Subfolder 2)
        - Lawsuit, Joseph Freeman vs. Rice Institute concerning land in the Thomas Tanner Survey, 1907-1909, 144930 (Box 32, Folder 12, Subfolder 3)
        - Contracts with A.A. Miller to look after land surveys in Newton Co., 1909-1911, 144929 (Box 32, Folder 12, Subfolder 4)
    - Parker County, 144924
      - Sale of land in Weatherford, Parker Co., 1908, 144926 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Sale, easement (Safeway Stores, Inc.) City of Weatherford to State of Texas, Parker Co., 1962, 144925 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Roberts County, 144922
      - Sale, 100 acres of Mary Peterson Survey to J.W. McCrary, Roberts Co., 1910-1911, 144923 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Robertson County, 144898
      - Title papers, Robertson Co., 1908, 144921 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Lease, 4 acres in Calvert to L.O. Closs, Robertson Co., 1950, 144920 (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - Lease, 106 acres in Calvert to John Stewart, Robertson Co., 1939-1946, 144919 (Box 33, Folder 6)